Guide to the David Hamburg papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Correspondence
  - Subseries III.1: Individuals
    - Vasconcellos, John, 1986-1988 (Box 340, Folder 12)
    - Vaughn, Warren T., 1979- (Box 340, Folder 13)
    - Verveer, Melanne, 1997-2000 (Box 340, Folder 14)
    - Verveer, Melanne, 1993-1998 (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Vest, Charles M., 1991-1998 (Box 341, Folder 2)
    - W (Box 346, Folder 10-11)
    - W (Box 347, Folder 1-3)
    - Wakeman, Frederic, 1989- (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Walch, Nancy, 1994-1996 (Box 341, Folder 5)
    - Walcher, Dwain, 1978-1979 (Box 341, Folder 6)
    - Wales, Jane, 1992-1998 (Box 341, Folder 7)
    - Walinsky, Adam, 1987-1995 (Box 341, Folder 8)
    - Wallis, John, 2000- (Box 341, Folder 9)
    - Walsh, Michael H., 1989-1994 (Box 341, Folder 10)
    - Walsh, Roger, 1977-1992 (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Walton, Henry, 1985-1994 (Box 342, Folder 2)
    - Ward, Antony, 1994-1997 (Box 342, Folder 3)
    - Ware, Donald, 1982-1997 (Box 342, Folder 4)
    - Warner, John W., 1985-1993 (Box 342, Folder 5)
    - Warren, Ken, 1979-1995 (Box 342, Folder 6)
    - Washburn, Sherwood, 1972-1993 (Box 342, Folder 7-8)
    - Watkins, James D., 1985-1999 (Box 342, Folder 9-10)
    - Waxman, Henry, 1984-1998 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Weisbrod, Burton, 1982-1996 (Box 343, Folder 2)
    - Weisfeld, Victoria, 1982-1984 (Box 343, Folder 3)
    - Weiss, Leonard, 1983-1992 (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Wells, Herman, 1991-1997 (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - West, Louis Jolyon, 1976-1987 (Box 343, Folder 6)
    - Westheimer, Frank H., 1977-1986 (Box 343, Folder 7)
    - Wetle, Terrie, 1982-2000 (Box 343, Folder 8)
    - Wharton, Clifton, 1985-1994 (Box 343, Folder 9)
    - Wharton, Clifton, 1977-1984 (Box 343, Folder 10)
    - White, Robert, 1960-1997 (Box 343, Folder 11)
    - Whitehead, John, 1988-1999 (Box 343, Folder 12)
    - Whitehead, John, 1984-1995 (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Widnall, Sheila, 1993-1998 (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Wien, Lawrence, 1983- (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Wiener, Malcolm and Shirley, 1993-2001 (Box 344, Folder 4)
    - Wiesel, Elie, 1987-2000 (Box 344, Folder 5)
    - Wiesel, Torsten, 1978-2000 (Box 344, Folder 6)
    - Wiesner, Jerome B, 1982-1996 (Box 344, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Eddie N, 1984-1995 (Box 344, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Franklin H, 1980-1987 (Box 344, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Luther, 1990-1995 (Box 344, Folder 10)
    - Williams, Shirley, 1991-1998 (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Williams, T. Franklin, 1987-1988 (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Francis, 1984-1998 (Box 345, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Julie, 1992-1999 (Box 345, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Linda S., 1983-1999 (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, William Julius, 1989-1999 (Box 345, Folder 6)
    - Wirth, Timothy, 1981-2001 (Box 345, Folder 7-10)
    - Wolfensohn, James D., 1995-2000 (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Wolman, M. Gordon, 1981-1994 (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Wolpe, Howard, 1984-1996 (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Wolstenhome, Gordon, 1986-1988 (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Wood, Suzanne, 1993-1996 (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Woodruff, Judy, 1991-1996 (Box 346, Folder 6)
    - Wrangham, Richard, 1975-2000 (Box 346, Folder 7)
    - Wuitchet, Pam, 1999-2000 (Box 346, Folder 9)
    - Wyngaarden, James, 1982-1991 (Box 346, Folder 8)
    - Y (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - Yarmolinsky, Adam, 1979-1999 (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Yarrow, Andrew, 1992-1996 (Box 347, Folder 5)
    - Yordy, Karl D., 1978-1993 (Box 347, Folder 6)
    - York, Herbert F., 1982-1984 (Box 347, Folder 7)
    - Young, Kathryn Taaffe, 1992-1995 (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Z (Box 348, Folder 9)
    - Zeckhauser, 1980-1991 (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Zeidenstein, George, 1983-1992 (Box 348, Folder 4)
    - Zhurkin, Vitaly, 1983-1987 (Box 348, Folder 5)
    - Zigler, Edward, 1991-2000 (Box 348, Folder 6)
    - Zinberg, Dorothy, 1993-1998 (Box 348, Folder 7)
    - Zorkin, Valery, 1993- (Box 348, Folder 8)
  - Subseries III.2: Institutions
    Contains external correspondence files with various institutions, such as universities, U.S. Government and U.N. agencies, academic and professional societies, non-profit organizations, The material in these files is often closely related to the one, in correspondence files for individuals, who were affiliated with these institutions (Series III.1). Several files in this sequence were found to be based not on institutions, but rather subjects, such as “Mental Health.” “VelHam” (integrated into the other Velikhov project materials in the Series I.8.C. of this collection).
    - 21st Century Commission on African American Males, 1991- (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Abraham Fund, 1996-1996 (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - Academic Medicine Development Company, 2001-2001 (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - Academy of Behavioral Medicine Research, 1980-1995 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - ADEPCON, 1999-1999 (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - AEA Investors Inc., 1996-1996 (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - African-American Institute, 1995-1995 (Box 349, Folder 7)
    - Agency for International Development, 1988-1988 (Box 349, Folder 8)
    - Alfred P Sloan Foundation, 1995-1995 (Box 349, Folder 9)
    - American Academy for Liberal Education, 1996-1996 (Box 349, Folder 10)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1985-1995 (Box 349, Folder 11)
    - American Academy of Child & Adolescent Psychiatry, 1976-1994 (Box 349, Folder 12)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics, 2000-2000 (Box 349, Folder 13)
    - American Agenda, 1988-1988 (Box 349, Folder 14)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1977-1998 (Box 349, Folder 15)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Correspondence, 1982-1995 (Box 350, Folder 1)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1985-1988 (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1984-1986 (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Material from William Wells, -31085 (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science: Testimony on NSF Budget Materials, -31098 (Box 350, Folder 5)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Speech Materials, -1985 (Box 350, Folder 6)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science Editorial Search, 1984-1984 (Box 351, Folder 1)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science Committee on Population, Resources and the Environment, 1984-1984 (Box 351, Folder 2)
    - American Bar Association, 1984-1984 (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - American Can Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 351, Folder 4)
    - American Ditchley Foundation, 1998-2001 (Box 351, Folder 5)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, 1991-1991 (Box 351, Folder 6)
    - American-Iranian Council, 2000-2000 (Box 351, Folder 7)
    - American Journal of Psychiatry, 1994-1994 (Box 351, Folder 8)
    - American Medical Association, 1988-1988 (Box 351, Folder 9)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1983-1996 (Box 351, Folder 10)
    - American Psychosomatic Society, 1999-1999 (Box 351, Folder 11)
    - American Psychosomatic Society, 1998-1999 (Box 351, Folder 12)
    - Amfar, 1995-1995 (Box 351, Folder 13)
    - Annenburg Foundation, 1991-1991 (Box 351, Folder 14)
    - Aspen Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 352)
    - Aspen Institute, 1994-1999 (Box 353)
    - Association of American Universities Presidents and Chancellors, 1995- (Box 354, Folder 1)
    - Atlantic Conference, 1988-1988 (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - Atlantic Council, 1996-1996 (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - Atlantic Fellowship in Public Policy, 1996-1996 (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - Avance, 1985-1999 (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - BankAmerica Foundation, 1981-1981 (Box 354, Folder 6)
    - Bank Street College of Education, 1996-1996 (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - Ben Gurion University of the Negev, 1983-1986 (Box 354, Folder 8)
    - Biological Sciences Curriculum Study, 1979-1983 (Box 354, Folder 9)
    - Board on Children Youth and Families, 1997-1997 (Box 354, Folder 10)
    - Brandeis University, 1982-1982 (Box 354, Folder 11)
    - Bright Beginnings, 1995-1995 (Box 354, Folder 12)
    - Brookings Institution, 1983-1999 (Box 354, Folder 13)
    - Brown University, 1994-1994 (Box 354, Folder 14)
    - Business Executives for National Security Inc., 1983-1992 (Box 354, Folder 15)
    - California Institute of Technology, 1976-1987 (Box 354, Folder 16)
    - Canon Society, 1979-1982 (Box 354, Folder 17)
    - CARE, 1997-1997 (Box 354, Folder 18)
    - Carnegie Council on Ethics and International Affairs, 2000-2000 (Box 354, Folder 19)
    - Carnegie Dunfermline Trust, 1992-1992 (Box 354, Folder 20)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1996-1996 (Box 355, Folder 1)
    - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1996-1996 (Box 355, Folder 2)
    - Carnegie Mellon, 1996-1996 (Box 355, Folder 3)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Board, 1998-1999 (Box 355, Folder 4)
    - Carnegie United Kingdom Trust, 1996-1996 (Box 355, Folder 5)
    - Catholic University of America, 1992-1992 (Box 355, Folder 6)
    - Center for Applied Special Technology, 1995-1996 (Box 355, Folder 7)
    - Center for Educational Outreach and Innovation, 1998-1998 (Box 355, Folder 8)
    - Center for Foreign Journalists, 1995-1995 (Box 355, Folder 9)
    - Center for Internation Health and Cooperation, 1994-1994 (Box 355, Folder 10)
    - Center for National Policy, 1995-1995 (Box 355, Folder 11)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1994-1994 (Box 355, Folder 12)
    - Center for Study of Professional Military Ethics, 1998-1998 (Box 356, Folder 1)
    - Center for the Advancement of Health, 1998-1998 (Box 356, Folder 2)
    - Charles A. Dana Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 356, Folder 3)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1986- (Box 356, Folder 4)
    - Chicago Children's Museum, 2000-2000 (Box 356, Folder 5)
    - Children of Alcoholics Foundation, 1984-1984 (Box 356, Folder 6)
    - Children's Defense Fund, 1994-1996 (Box 356, Folder 7)
    - Children's Institute International, 1996-1996 (Box 356, Folder 8)
    - Children's Roundtable, 1993-1993 (Box 356, Folder 9)
    - Children's Television Workshop, 1996-1996 (Box 356, Folder 10)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1995-1995 (Box 357, Folder 1)
    - Churchill Center for Learning Disabilities, 1983-1984 (Box 357, Folder 2)
    - Citizen's Network for Foreign Affairs, 1996-1996 (Box 357, Folder 3)
    - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1995-1995 (Box 357, Folder 4)
    - Colorado Project, -ND (Box 357, Folder 5)
    - Columbia University, 1991-1997 (Box 357, Folder 6)
    - Committee on Contributions of Behavioral and Social Science to the Prevention of Nuclear War, 1988-1988 (Box 357, Folder 7)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1982-1997 (Box 357, Folder 8)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1971-1976 (Box 357, Folder 9)
    - Communitarian Network, 1996-1996 (Box 357, Folder 10)
    - Community Schools, -ND (Box 357, Folder 11)
    - Conflict Management Group, 1993-1993 (Box 357, Folder 12)
    - Cornell University, 1998-1999 (Box 357, Folder 13)
    - Cosmos Club, 1994-1995 (Box 357, Folder 14)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers, 1995-1996 (Box 357, Folder 15)
    - Council on Competitiveness, 1996-1996 (Box 357, Folder 16)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1999-2001 (Box 357, Folder 17)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1983-2001 (Box 358)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1997-2003 (Box 359)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1992-1995 (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - Council on Foreign Relations - Center for Preventative Action, 2000-2000 (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - Council on Foundations, 1985-2001 (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - Council on Religion and International Affairs, 1986-1986 (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - Dance Theater of Harlem, 1993-1993 (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - Danforth Foundation, 1995-1995 (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - Defense Policy Board, 1994-1997 (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - Democracy in Africa, 1994-1994 (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - Ditchley Foundation (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - Ditchley Foundation, 1988-1996 (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - Donner Canadian Foundation, 1984-1984 (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - Doris Duke Foundation, 1997-1997 (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - Duke University, 1997-1997 (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - Economic Policy Institute, 1997-1997 (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1999-1999 (Box 362, Folder 6)
    - Emory University, 1995-1995 (Box 362, Folder 7)
    - Eurasia Foundation, 1996-1996 (Box 362, Folder 8)
    - European Ditchley Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - Fairchild Foundation, 1981-1981 (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - Federal Reserve, 1994-1995 (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - Federal Reserve, 1994-1995 (Box 364)
    - Flexner Award, 1991-1991 (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - Families and Work Initiative, 1995-1995 (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - Field Museum, 1996-1996 (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - Fisher Foundation, 1999-1999 (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - Fleischmann Foundation, 1972-1980 (Box 365, Folder 5)
    - Fogg Art Museum, 1981-1981 (Box 365, Folder 6)
    - Food Research Institute, 1995-1995 (Box 365, Folder 7)
    - Ford Foundation, 1983-1996 (Box 365, Folder 8)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1998-2001 (Box 365, Folder 9)
    - Foundation Executives Group, 1992-1996 (Box 365, Folder 10)
    - Foundation Executives Group, 1987-1995 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - Foundation for Child Development (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - Fundacion Mexicana para la Salud, 1996-1997 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - Fund for Peace, 1998-1998 (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - George Washington University, 1998-1998 (Box 366, Folder 5)
    - Hazen Awards, 1983-1985 (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - Hebrew University, 1994-1994 (Box 366, Folder 7)
    - Heinz Awards (Box 366, Folder 8)
    - Heinz Awards, 1995-1999 (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - Heinz Endowments, 1997-1997 (Box 367, Folder 2)
    - Helpage International, 2000-2002 (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - Hewlett Foundation, 1998-2001 (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - Independent Sector, 1994-1995 (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - Indiana University, 1996-1997 (Box 368, Folder 2)
    - Institute for Advanced Study, 1996-1997 (Box 368, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Multi-Track Diplomacy, 1997-1997 (Box 368, Folder 4)
    - Institute for the Study of Smoking Behavior, 1984-1984 (Box 368, Folder 5)
    - Inter-American Dialogue, 1995-1996 (Box 368, Folder 6)
    - IBM Film, -ND (Box 368, Folder 7)
    - International Development Research Center, 1991-1995 (Box 368, Folder 8)
    - International Development Research Center, 1990-1994 (Box 368, Folder 9)
    - International Peace Academy, 1994-2000 (Box 368, Folder 10)
    - International Peace Academy, 2000-2002 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - International Peace Research Institute, 1996-1996 (Box 369, Folder 2)
    - International Research and Exchanges Board (IREX), 1996-1996 (Box 369, Folder 3)
    - International Society for Research on Aggression, 1972-1984 (Box 369, Folder 4)
    - Internews, 1996-1996 (Box 369, Folder 5)
    - IVAX Corporation, 1988-1988 (Box 369, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Healthcare Foundation, 1996-1996 (Box 369, Folder 7)
    - John Heinz Regional History Center, 1995-1995 (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - Joint Center for Political and Economic Studies, 1997-1997 (Box 370, Folder 2)
    - Jonas Salk Foundation, 1997-1997 (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Judge Baker Children's Center, 1995-1995 (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Kellogg Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - Kettering Foundation, 1983-1996 (Box 370, Folder 6)
    - LAMBO Foundation, 1982-1985 (Box 370, Folder 7)
    - Lasker Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 370, Folder 8)
    - League of Women Voters, 1983-1984 (Box 370, Folder 9)
    - Leakey Foundation, 1982-1990 (Box 370, Folder 10)
    - Liz Clairborne/Art Ortenburg Foundation, 1993-1993 (Box 370, Folder 11)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1980-1997 (Box 371, Folder 1)
    - MacArthur Foundation - Palme/Brundtland Meeting, 1990-1990 (Box 371, Folder 2)
    - March of Dimes, 2000-2000 (Box 372, Folder 1)
    - Massachusets Institute of Technology (MIT), 1991-1998 (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - Mellon Foundation, 1981-1981 (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - Mental Health, 1995-1995 (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - Mental Health Law Project, 1992- (Box 372, Folder 5)
    - Michigan State University, 1986-1992 (Box 372, Folder 6)
    - Minnesota Project on Corporate Responsibility, 1987-1987 (Box 372, Folder 7)
    - Monterey Institute of International Studies, 1997-1997 (Box 372, Folder 8)
    - National Academy of Engineering, 1996-1996 (Box 372, Folder 9)
    - National Board for Professional Teaching Standards, 1995-1995 (Box 372, Folder 10)
    - National Campaign to Prevent Teen Pregnancy, 1995-1996 (Box 373)
    - National Campaign to Prevent Teen Pregnancy, 1996-1998 (Box 374)
    - National Campaign to Prevent Teen Pregnancy, 1995-1998 (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - National Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse at Columbia University, 1996-1997 (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - National Center for Children in Poverty, 1993-1996 (Box 375, Folder 3)
    - National Commission on Civic Renewal, 1996-1996 (Box 375, Folder 4)
    - National Commission on Teaching and America's Future, 1995-1995 (Box 375, Folder 5)
    - National Committee on Higher Education and the Health of Youth, 1997-1997 (Box 375, Folder 6)
    - National Consortium on Violence Research, 1996-1997 (Box 375, Folder 7)
    - National Council for International Health, 1995-1995 (Box 375, Folder 8)
    - National Council on Alcoholism, 1985-1986 (Box 375, Folder 9)
    - National Endowment for Democracy, 1997-1997 (Box 375, Folder 10)
    - National Governer's Association, 1995-1997 (Box 376, Folder 1)
    - National Institute for Dispute Resolution, 1994-1994 (Box 376, Folder 2)
    - National Mentoring Partnerships, 1996-1997 (Box 376, Folder 3)
    - National Public Radio, 1983-1983 (Box 376, Folder 4)
    - National Research Council, 1993-1997 (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - National Resources Defense Council, 1987-1995 (Box 376, Folder 6)
    - National Science Foundation, 1986-1995 (Box 376, Folder 7)
    - National Security Council, 1995-1995 (Box 376, Folder 8)
    - National Urban League, 1980-1996 (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Native American Science Education Association, 1988-1988 (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - New York Academy of Medicine, 1996-1998 (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - New York Academy of Sciences, 1991-1998 (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - New York Times, 1984-1984 (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - New York University, 1995-1997 (Box 377, Folder 6)
    - Nobel Peace Prize, 1999- (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - Nuclear Threat Initiative, 1995-1996 (Box 378, Folder 1)
    - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), 1985-1986 (Box 378, Folder 2)
    - Overseas Development Council, 1995-1996 (Box 378, Folder 3)
    - Packard Foundation, 1994-1996 (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - Pan-American Health Organisation, 1995-1997 (Box 379, Folder 1)
    - Partnership for Children's Health, 1998-1999 (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - Penn State Visiting Committee, 1997-1997 (Box 379, Folder 3)
    - Pfizer, 1985-1985 (Box 379, Folder 4)
    - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - Pius XII Foundation, 1996-1996 (Box 379, Folder 6)
    - Project on Ethnic Relations, 1997-1997 (Box 379, Folder 7)
    - Public Education Foundation, 1987-1996 (Box 379, Folder 8)
    - Public Radio, 1993-1995 (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - Pugwash Conferences on Science and World Affairs, 1978-2000 (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - Quality Education for Minorities, 1990-1996 (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - Radcliffe College, 1994-1997 (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - Radcliffe College, 1995-2000 (Box 381)
    - RAND, 1990-1997 (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1985-1996 (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1982-1995 (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - Russia Meeting, 1995-1995 (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - Role of American Military Power, 2000-2000 (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - Second Nature, 1995-1995 (Box 383, Folder 3)
    - Sigma Theta Tau International, 1995-1996 (Box 383, Folder 4)
    - Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society, 1986-1996 (Box 383, Folder 5)
    - Smithsonian Musem, 1985-1985 (Box 383, Folder 6)
    - Society for Adolescent Medicine, 1994-1994 (Box 383, Folder 7)
    - Society for Research in Child Development, 1997-1997 (Box 383, Folder 8)
    - Southern Africa Grantmaker's Affinity Group, 1997-1997 (Box 383, Folder 9)
    - Special Projects Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 383, Folder 10)
    - Spencer Foundation, 1997-1997 (Box 383, Folder 11)
    - Stimson Center, 1994-1995 (Box 383, Folder 12)
    - State of the World Forum, 1996-1998 (Box 383, Folder 13)
    - State of the World Forum, 1996-1998 (Box 384, Folder 1)
    - Strengthening American Democracy, 1996-1996 (Box 384, Folder 2)
    - Suchard Foundation, 1989- (Box 384, Folder 3)
    - Talk Radio, 1995-1995 (Box 384, Folder 4)
    - Teacher's College, 1998-2000 (Box 384, Folder 5)
    - Teacher's College Hechinger Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 384, Folder 6)
    - Teaching Matters Inc, 1995-1995 (Box 384, Folder 7)
    - Tel Aviv University, 1979-1983 (Box 384, Folder 8)
    - Thomas Watson Jr Institute for International Studies, 1998-1998 (Box 385, Folder 1)
    - Treasury, Dept of, 1996-1996 (Box 385, Folder 2)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1997-1997 (Box 385, Folder 3)
    - Uniformed Services University of the Health Sciences, Department of Defense, 1977-1977 (Box 385, Folder 4)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1998-1998 (Box 385, Folder 5)
    - UNICEF, 1989-1995 (Box 385, Folder 6)
    - United Nations Association of the United States of America, 1996-1997 (Box 385, Folder 7)
    - United Nations Association of the United States of America (Box 386, Folder 1)
    - UNESCO, -ND (Box 386, Folder 2)
    - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees, 1996-1997 (Box 386, Folder 3)
    - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees, 1995-1997 (Box 387, Folder 4)
    - United Nations High Level Advisory Board on Sustainable Development, 1996-1997 (Box 387, Folder 5)
    - United Nations High Level Advisory Board on Sustainable Development, 1989-1996 (Box 388, Folder 1)
    - United States Department of State, 1996-1997 (Box 388, Folder 2)
    - United States Institute of Peace, 1997-1997 (Box 388, Folder 3)
    - United States Postal Commission, 2000-2000 (Box 388, Folder 4)
    - United States Postal Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 389, Folder 1)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1995-1996 (Box 389, Folder 2)
    - University of California, Los Angeles/USC Gerontology Center, 1981-1981 (Box 389, Folder 3)
    - University of California, San Francisco, 1998-1998 (Box 389, Folder 4)
    - University of California, 1995-1996 (Box 389, Folder 5)
    - University of Cape Town, 1995-1997 (Box 389, Folder 6)
    - University of Florida, 1978-1999 (Box 389, Folder 7)
    - University of Michigan, 1996-1998 (Box 390, Folder 1)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1995-1997 (Box 390, Folder 2)
    - Urban Institute, 1986-1995 (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - Villers Foundation, 1982-1982 (Box 391, Folder 1)
    - Voice of America, 1994-1995 (Box 391, Folder 2)
    - W.A. Benjamin, Inc, 1977-1977 (Box 391, Folder 3)
    - Wenner-Gren Foundation, 1977-1981 (Box 391, Folder 4)
    - William T. Grant Foundation, 1996-1996 (Box 391, Folder 5)
    - Woman's National Democratic Club, 1994-1994 (Box 391, Folder 6)
    - World Bank, 1996-1996 (Box 391, Folder 7)
    - World Bank, 1995-1997 (Box 392, Folder 1)
    - World Bank Global Knowledge '97, 1997-1997 (Box 392, Folder 2)
    - World Bank Global Knowledge '97, 1997-1997 (Box 393, Folder 1)
    - World Communications Year 1983, 1983-1984 (Box 393, Folder 2)
    - World Health Organization, 1977-1997 (Box 393, Folder 3)